leaf2 = [
{"question":"深怕","Answer":"shēnpà"},
{"question":"吵醒","Answer":"chǎoxǐng"},
{"question":"瓊絲","Answer":"qióngsī"},
{"question":"哨","Answer":"shào"},
{"question":"擺","Answer":"bǎi"},
{"question":"畫板","Answer":"huàbǎn"},
{"question":"微弱","Answer":"wēiruò"},
{"question":"睜","Answer":"zhēng"},
{"question":"專注 ","Answer":"zhuānzhù  "},
{"question":"喃喃自語","Answer":"nánnán zìyǔ"},
{"question":"倒數","Answer":"dàoshù"},
{"question":"左顧右盼","Answer":"zuǒgùyòu pàn"},
{"question":"到底","Answer":"dàodǐ"},
{"question":"氣若游絲","Answer":"qìruòyóusī"},
{"question":"頭疼","Answer":"tóuténg"},
{"question":"片","Answer":"piàn"},
{"question":"爬山虎","Answer":"páshānhǔ"},
{"question":"落盡","Answer":"luòjìn"},
{"question":"傻瓜","Answer":"shǎguā"},
{"question":"責備","Answer":"zébèi"},
{"question":"語氣","Answer":"yǔqì"},
{"question":"季節","Answer":"jìjié"},
{"question":"變換","Answer":"biànhuàn"},
{"question":"掉落","Answer":"diàoluò"},
{"question":"復","Answer":"fù"},
{"question":"原 ","Answer":"yuán  "},
{"question":"唉","Answer":"āi"},
{"question":"不經大腦","Answer":"bùjīng dànǎo"},
{"question":"無益","Answer":"wúyì"},
{"question":"然","Answer":"rán"},
{"question":"卻","Answer":"què"},
{"question":"掉落","Answer":"diàoluò"},
{"question":"剩","Answer":"shèng"},
{"question":"圖畫","Answer":"túhuà"},
{"question":"連","Answer":"lián"},
{"question":"牀邊","Answer":"chuáng biān"},
{"question":"閉","Answer":"bì"},
{"question":"蒼白 ","Answer":"cāngbái  "},
{"question":"模樣","Answer":"múyàng"},
{"question":"雕像","Answer":"diāoxiàng"},
{"question":"病魔","Answer":"bìngmó"},
{"question":"搏鬥","Answer":"bódòu"},
{"question":"放棄","Answer":"fàngqì"},
{"question":"淒涼","Answer":"qīliáng"},
{"question":"終究","Answer":"zhōngjiū"},
{"question":"難過","Answer":"nánguò"},
{"question":"話題","Answer":"huàtí"},
{"question":"趕緊","Answer":"gǎnjǐn"},
{"question":"貝阿蒙","Answer":"bèi āméng"},
{"question":"模特兒","Answer":"mótè r"}
]